

4th year undergraduate

19 Yuquan Road (a), Snijingsnan District, Beijing Beijing, Beijing heyinhan18@gmail.com

I am a student aiming to explore in machine learning and artifitial intelligence, especially data mining. With a four-year applied mathematics undergradute program which equips me solid backgraound in mathematics and fluency in programming, I could dig deep into machine learning models to find out some math principles burried under the surface and figure out new models that perform better. Besides, I am also friendly and helpful, always ready to be a good partner in cooperation.

Professional Experience

July 2021 - Present Research Intern Institute of Automation(CAS)

I mainly focus on studying oversmoothing problem of relation-aware graph convolutional neural network, including its

theoratical cause, measurement and rational&powerful solutions toward this issue.

January 2021 - June 2021

Visit Student National University of Singapore

I was funded by home university to have a one semester exchange progam, I took some stat&CS modules, and also took a thai language module. This experience equips me with fluent programming skills, deeper view in data analysing and art of cooperating with people from different culture background.

Education

September 2018 -Present

B.S. in mathematics and applied mathematics University of Chinese Academy of Sciences at Beijing, P.R. China

Key Skills

- Programming methodology: C, C++, python(most frequently used)
- Mathematics(Calculus, Algebra, Probability, Stochastic Process, Functional Analysis, etc)
- · Artifitial Intelligence/ Machine learning Basics
- Comfortable with Pytorch frameworks
- · Fluent in both English and Chinese (Listening, Speaking, Reading & Writing)

Accomplishments

- University Scholarship (twice)
- Outstanidng student & Outstanding student leader (twice)
- Student representitive of 1st Student Congress
- Student department secretary, college of mathematical sciences(cls 2018)
- Served as Minister of the Organization Department of Student Union